is amazing though just like technology
and everywhere and like the future of
what we can do like now you can order
any food you want and it will come to
you isn't that amazing whatever you want
and you just get it like any like with
all the different food order places you
just put whatever you want and somebody
will bring it to you it's amazing
because before for like 150 years you
could just order pizza that was the only
place I figured out how to deliver food
for some reason
they found the technology early
they're like yeah you just put it in a
box and then you bring it to the person
and then other food places were like
that'll never work
and then and then like 2017 rolled
around and they're like oh yeah you just
put it in a box and you bring it to them
it works
just don't put the chicken in a pizza
box you just get a different size box
totally works
the pizza they're always one step ahead
on technology they always are they're
like because my favorite place to order
from is Domino's yeah I like to order
there because they have the pizza
tracker oh yeah the Visa tracker is
amazing they uh when you order your
pizza they go now go check the tracker
and it's just the thing online that just
gives you step-by-step instruction of
what's happening to your pizza it's
incredible so you order the pizza and
you look at the tracker and it'll be
like John just put the toppings on your
pizza he's pretty excited about it
I'm like way to go John thanks for doing
that oh you're the best John
and then a little later you're checking
it'll be like Luis just put your pizza
in the oven it's bubbly hot I'm like oh
that's fantastic Louise thank you for
doing that I don't know why John could
have done that but I'm glad you're in
the game
I'm not gonna tell you how to run this
business
and then it's like Sarah's on the way
with your pizza like I can't wait to
meet Sarah this is gonna be fantastic
I'm gonna ask her about Luis and John
when she gets here
I really want updates on those guys
a funny thing about Domino's though they
have a rule where you can order you can
only order 25 marinara packets
this is the cutoff 25 they had a meeting
at corporate they're like that's enough
for a human 25
Mariner packages plenty
but the weird thing is you don't have to
order a pizza you can just order
marinara packets
that's the thing you can do yeah the
tracker changes a little bit though it's
like John's putting your marinara
packets in a bag right now and he's a
little confused not gonna lie foreign
your house with the marinara packets and
she's thinking about making some changes
in her life
she might go back to school
and you just gotta answer the door of
the Mason jar like here we go fill her
up
he's here
foreign